(Amy:)You guys comfy?
This might take a while.
You know, I don't
understand why women
(Sheldon:)insist on making
a big production
(Sheldon:)out of buying clothes.
(Penny:)No, you're right,
we should do what you do.
(Penny:)Have our mom send us pants
from the Walmart in Houston.
(Sheldon:)They have a man there
(Sheldon:)who understands
my personal style.
(Penny:)Bye.
(Leonard:)Uh, I've got some bad news.
(Leonard:)There's no cell service in here.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Well, that's all right.
(Sheldon:)There were plenty of ways
to pass the time
(Sheldon:)before smart phones
were invented.
(Leonard:)That's true.
(Sheldon:)I'll look them up.
(Sheldon:)Son of a biscuit.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, it's fine.
(Sheldon:)No, it's not fine.
(Sheldon:)What kind of store
in the 21st century
(Sheldon:)doesn't at least have Wi-Fi?
(Sheldon:)I'm going to call
their corporate office...
Son of a biscuit!
(Sheldon:)Let's see, my armies
(Sheldon:)are going
to attack the Shire